aber.ac.uk 2019-12-02

# Aberystwyth University - Cookie Policy

We put small files known as ‘cookies’ onto your computer to collect information about how your browse our website.

## Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to collect web site usage information. We do this to make sure that the site is meeting the needs of our users and to help us make improvements. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect this information. Google Analytics does not collect any personal information. More information is available in [Google’s privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-GB).

## Crazy Egg

We us Crazy Egg to collect web site usage information. We do this to make sure that the site is meeting the needs of our users and to help us make improvements. Crazy Egg uses cookies to collect this information. Crazy Egg does not collect any personal information. More information is available in [Crazy Egg’s privacy policy](https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy).

## GeckoEngage

Our Open Day form is provided by a 3rd party called GeckoEngage. They use cookies to track the performance of the Open Day form and provide data which helps us to improve our site. More information is available in [GeckoEngage’s privacy policy](https://www.geckoengage.com/privacy-policy/).

## Campaign Partners

We use campaign partners to help us with advertising and targeting for specific events. These partners use cookies to track how many users arrive at our site from the advertisements that they control.

## Facebook

Some pages on our site contain Facebook ‘pixels’. These are small pieces of code that allow Facebook to record data when a user comes to our site from an advert on Facebook. These pixels set cookies when you visit the pages they are in. No personal information is stored in the cookie. More information is available in [Facebook’s Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/).

## YouTube

We use YouTube to provide videos on some pages of the site. YouTube sets cookies when you visit one of these pages. The cookies are used by YouTube to track views of videos, and keep track of user preferences and interests. More information is available in [Google’s privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-GB).

## Session Cookies

When you use a web application on our site, we often use session cookies to remember your choices. These cookies are removed when you close your browser and no personal information is stored.

## Managing Cookies

Information on managing cookies from the Information Commissioner’s Office: <https://ico.org.uk/your-data-matters/online/cookies/>
